directathletics.com 2001-12-12

# DirectAthletics.com

|  |  |   
We are committed to safeguarding the online privacy of our users, and recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of personal information collected. This policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically.  
---  
**COLLECTION OF INFORMATION**  
Our site's registration form requests users to give us contact information (like your name, graduation year, etc.). Some of the requested information is required in order to receive the DirectAthletics.com service; other information is optional. The required information is clearly marked as such on the registration pages. DirectAthletics collects personal information on users primarily for the administrative uses of coaches and administrators. Only authorized administrators and a user’s current coach may view personal information submitted by a user within the site. By collecting this information, administrators can better monitor their users, and keep better track of users with handicaps or special medical conditions. Coaches will be able to view their athletes’ contact information on their online roster for convenience purposes only.  
We do not share any of your information with third parties without your permission. During the registration process, you may grant permission for us to share your contact and profile information with third parties or sponsors, generally companies which sell consumer products and services about which our users may be interested. The option for granting this permission is clearly marked on the registration pages. We may also provide you with opportunities at other times to receive information about additional products and services, but we will never share your information with third parties unless you grant us permission to do so. If you grant us permission to share your information with third parties, and then change your mind, you may revoke your permission at any time by going to your profile in Setup within your account. 

You will not receive any communications from DirectAthletics or third parties, unless you explicitly "opt-in" during the registration process. You may opt-in by checking the box marked "Yes, send me e-mail and other special offers and promotions from third parties (groups other than DirectAthletics) that may be of interest to me" in the account creation process or by going to Setup within your account.  
  
DirectAthletics or its affiliates may be collecting or tracking personal information on its users, either by asking you to tell us something about yourself (for example, when you input your name, address, and email address during the registration process), or by using software that tells us what advertisements or parts of the site have been of interest to you. Information about your activities may also be collected on an aggregate (i.e., group) basis, where we will not know or keep track of precisely who you are.  
Please be aware that advertisements displayed on the DirectAthletics site or third party web sites which are linked from the DirectAthletics site may also collect information about you. The information practices of those advertisers and web sites are outside of our control and are not covered by this privacy policy.  
**SUBSCRIBER SERVICES AND REGISTRATION DATA**  
In order to access certain Subscriber Services within the site, you may be asked to provide Registration Data through an online registration form. You will then be supplied with a "username" and "password." The information collected may include your legal name, address, telephone number, birthday, email address, subscriber name or areas of interest, and/or password used to access Subscriber Services. DirectAthletics reserves the right to request any additional information necessary to establish and maintain your account for use of the Subscriber Services.  
Registration Data is in part the property of DirectAthletics. In some instances, DirectAthletics may use your Registration Data on an aggregate (i.e., group) basis, where we will not know or keep track of individual information. For example, we may use zip codes to display different advertisements on the site to users in different geographical areas. Should you wish, users may "opt-in", or choose at your own discretion, to receive email with promotions and special offers from third parties (groups other than DirectAthletics). This is entirely optional, and users can opt-out of releasing all of their information at any time by going to the Setup in their account.  
We do not endorse the practice of sending unsolicited commercial e-mail (spam). If you grant us permission as described above, DirectAthletics may share your information on an aggregate basis with third parties for the purpose of sending you e-mails with special offers and promotions that we think may be of interest to you. We will not share your information with third parties for resale, unauthorized reuse, or for any other purposes we deem inappropriate for our users. E-mails sent from, or in association with, third parties will be in close partnership with DirectAthletics.  
Use of the DirectAthletics site is conditioned on your provision of requested information in an accurate and truthful fashion. If you choose not to provide such information, you may not be able to access some or all of the site. Although DirectAthletics will use all reasonable efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of the Registration Data, transmissions made by means of the Internet cannot be guaranteed to be secure. DirectAthletics has no liability for disclosure of Registration Data due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties.  
**ACCESS TO PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
DirectAthletics displays limited information about athlete users within its site. This information includes team affiliation and graduation year, as well as any publicly-available athletic results. This information may be viewed by all users in the site.  
Only teammates, coaches and administrators who represent teams or leagues with which an athlete is affiliated may view additional information including, but not limited to, address, phone number, email address, and birthday.  
Medical information is distributed only as needed to authorized administrators. Under no circumstances will any medical information be disclosed to parties other than authorized athletic administrators.  
|
